they want
eat 1 truffle?
I took the chevas to polish and then it started to rain.
I said, bro,
I'm going to fix a cape and now he's here.
O to keep preserved.
Good morning bro speaking softly because I have an idea
I try to sell this to the owner of the gas station.
Bro,
I hope it works.
wishing me luck
O Caio.
You go there having a cappuccino,
you see.
My idea is that I'm responsible,
I stop there,
but then I needed to see with you.
It makes sense it took a while,
right?
Okay?
And now we're going into the background.
There will be walking.
Now I'm going to bro,
because I skipped the car.
Interesting is you.
When you are going to sell a product,
don't use it anymore,
leave it time to draw the attention of a possible buyer.
Oh,
sorry for the delay.
How are you?
I came to leave a little replacement truffles
and make an invitation for you to take.
Someone else can take it,
but it's that first.
It will only be for cash guests.
Grandpa,
here at the money store.
Thanks.
You are wonderful girls send close Tide guys slope we are together bye bye bye
it's worth everything good talk bro you're fine from the pharmacy bro
only for the guest you can stick we're together ok we have 1 lot of
delivery to do there and there's 1 deal on the beard,
see if I can give 1 deal on the beard too,
because tomorrow I have to go to São Paulo for an event and then you'll
know where I'm going and because I'm going there in São Paulo and then my dear,
are you ok?
You are all invited and everyone else 1 barbershop
here now closing the truffles.
Let's go hand in hand.
So I'm doing this just to invite you.
People I know are going to be more like that.
Closed.
, forty people.
Are you on?
I know you're so into the cut,
but that's what's getting the invitation,
bro.
Got a little knack now on the beard,
o caraca.
Now I'm stuck
Non-human.